# Roman Kholodkov

Kiryat Motzkin, Haifa District, Israel



chikitonik@gmail.com



+972504694780



linkedin.com/in/roman-kholodkov

## **Summary**

I am a SAP ERP specialist and full-stack developer with 8 years of experience in SAP ERP support. My expertise lies in providing comprehensive support and troubleshooting solutions for SAP ERP systems. My portfolio, which can be found at https://chikitonik.github.io, showcases my work and projects.

#### Languages:

- English: Upper-Intermediate

- Hebrew: Alef+- Russian: Native

I am a passionate programmer with experience in JavaScript, Python, ABAP, and VBA. I enjoy working with these languages to develop innovative solutions and optimize processes. In addition to my technical skills, I am a dedicated and disciplined professional with a strong analytical mindset and a sense of responsibility. I am non-confrontational, responsive, and punctual, making me a reliable team member. I hold a driver's license and have a range of interests outside of work, including sports and DIY activities.

## **Experience**

## SAP Specialist

ГК Армтек

Jul 2018 - Present (4 years 11 months)

Working in the second line of SAP technical support in SD and MM modules, providing e-store support and API requests

#### Main responsibility:

- working with users requests: searching and fixing problems providing the necessary accesses consulting on web requests
- teaching users
- making the settings in the system for new commercial objects
- replication solutions to other retail facilities
- writing instructions for users
- writing regulatory documents for users as to work in Z transactions

#### For all SAP modules:

- skills in debugging and reading ABAP code
- preparing loaders using LSMW
- working with tables in SE16N
- creating reports in SQ01 with ABAP code
- testing new reports and programs in SAP

### Additionally:

- support e-store functionality and API integration

### SAP Specialist

#### Bezant

Jun 2015 - Jun 2018 (3 years 1 month) Supporting and training of users in FI, MM, SD, WMS

#### For all modules:

- skills in working with the debugger and reading ABAP code
- preparation of instructions for users, keeping them up-to-date
- preparation of loaders in LSMW
- working with tables in SE16N
- organization of data transfer between SAP and other enterprise management systems
- participation in SAP implementation, organization of data migration
- testing new reports and programs in SAP

#### Additionally:

- training users in Excel skills
- writing macros for processing data in Excel (many projects, such as processing customer orders, processing invoices and packages, compiling reports, etc)
- creating SQL queries for databases
- writing small programs in JAVA for specific needs

## **Key Account Manager**

#### Bezant

Mar 2007 - Jun 2015 (8 years 4 months)

Sales support and analysis of the key clients as METRO Cash & Carry, Castorama, Lenta, Real

### **Education**

## O Developers.Institute

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp - JavaScript

Sep 2022 - Mar 2023

https://developers.institute/en/portfolios/best-coding-bootcamp-tel-aviv-israel/

### **Practicum USA**

**Data Science** 

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

https://practicum.com/data-scientist

### Saratov State University named after N.G.Chernyshevsky

Master's degree, Geography

#### Skills

Full-Stack Development • SAP Sales & Distribution • SAP ERP